{
    "subject": "resource/Estonia",
    "predicate": "ontology/leaderTitle",
    "object": "President",
    "human_readable": "The leader title of Estonia is President.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9042121767997742,
            "question": "What is the title of the leader of Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7426905632019043,
            "question": "What is the name given to the leader of Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7151935696601868,
            "question": "Who leads Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5972957015037537,
            "question": "What word describes the leader of Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5500419735908508,
            "question": "What is the official title for the Estonian head of government?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5116090774536133,
            "question": "Who presides over Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41447320580482483,
            "question": "What position governs Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4005407392978668,
            "question": "What title represents the highest political office in Estonia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16998273134231567,
            "question": "What term describes the Estonian head of state?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14315862953662872,
            "question": "What position holds the highest authority in Estonia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The leader title of Estonia is President.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8399_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What term describes the Estonian head of state?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8399_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What title represents the highest political office in Estonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8399_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position governs Estonia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8399_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8399_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. According to the context, Kaja Kallas is mentioned as the Prime Minister of Estonia, but later on, Alar Karis is mentioned as the President of Estonia. However, it also mentions that Kaja Kallas' father was part of the Estonian independence movement and served as the country's Prime Minister (2002-2003). This implies that there can be a leader with the title \"Prime Minister\" in Estonia, but Alar Karis is indeed mentioned as the President."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that the leader title in Estonia is President. This can be inferred from the information provided, particularly in the document with file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8399/re-ranker-msmarco/133.txt`, which details the role and responsibilities of the President of the Republic of Estonia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}